<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>English</title>
        <description>Articulate literary works by diligent students</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self"
        type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 11:15:56 +0530</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 11:15:56 +0530</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
        
        <item>
            <title>Revelation</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revelation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I smiled gazing at the moon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An epiphany occurred: Rose are made of diamonds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides a diamond a flower bloomed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A diamond will cherish the mood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but a flower cannot cure the gloom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more valuable?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A crippled lifeless diamond or …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An alive and exuberant rose which blooms in the morning and withers by the evening&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love is like a fresh fragrant breeze that enters the home, fills it with freshness and fragrance, remains there as long as existence allow it, then moves out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you close all the doors the same breeze will become absolutely stale&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In life everything is changing and change is beautiful&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gives you more experience, more awareness and more maturity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You bestow the vivacity of a rose; full of exuberance and euphoria&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a moonlight solacing the existence with luminance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking of you teleports me to Atlantis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing fancy, just ordinary things about you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right perspective converts stones into sermons&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re like an antidote who blows away the melancholy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want possessions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you love a rose, don’t pluck it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love is not about possession, it’s about appreciation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little faith, just a little trust&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if you believe in love, it can move mountains&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An alchemy which can turn anything into gold like a Midas touch&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I wanna quit, your thought keeps me going&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You strengthen my endurance and keep me disciplined&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The glimmer on your face is breath taking&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The simplicity of your being is magnanimous&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vivacity of your soul is just par excellence!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It makes my intuition whispers, it’s you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/25/revelation.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/25/revelation.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Talisman Jerry</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talisman Jerry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are like a talisman, Jerry ;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Classic like blackberry;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her presence is luminary;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is not ordinary;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But legendary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just extra ordinary;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her aims are revolutionary ;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is a Happiness dictionary ;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You make everyone go crazy,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way you carry Yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a beautiful and cute fairy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sometimes you are January&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes February&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are just honorary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your aura is not temporary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a great visionary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are primarily sweet raspberry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondarily a great savour cherry
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you walk into the library&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You be a addictive book like cantaberry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A placebo who blows my worry,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rarely i never think of you,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always miss you,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a living glory,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are melodious than L.P(Linkin Park)’s Hybrid theory,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You make me forget the pivotal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game theory and Big bang theory
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When to the inner force I do the enquiry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My inner voice whispers your name jerry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your names are sweeter than heaven.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have an indispensable place in my Memory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has a Little dictionary filled with your memories&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your beauty is expansionary,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Increasingly regularly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a graph exponentially,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your aura transcends me to a blissful stage which is Illusionary and imaginary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are Inter disciplinary,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blend of excellence and elegance
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cast a spell better than wizard Potter the Harry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For times for my blunders i am sorry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever my aims are blurry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So make me visionary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your glimpse is vulnerary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Than any military&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your make it look like your looks are greater&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Than god aries
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucky and fortunate is ur teddy
Jeleous of him&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cause its evolutionary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When i query my mind i get the answer jerry and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember the “hihihi” which is really like a fairy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of the above is contrary,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just i expressed my convictions altogether&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what i feel literary.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/24/talisman-jerry.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/24/talisman-jerry.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Moonlight Revelation</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moonlight Revelation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your gaze penetrates me like the moonlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serene, tranquil and calm just like the moonlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You bestow the vivacity of a rose; full of exuberance and euphoria&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a moonlight solacing the existence with luminance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking of you teleports me to Atlantis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this world full of luxury and indulgence, I am fond of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am passionate about you, I’m thunderstruck by you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s illogical, beyond logic from a higher realm of intuition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For It cannot apprehend enthusiasm and altruism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My intuition whispered it’s you, who makes me courageous and alive&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking of you I forget all my worries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no past nor future, just this indispensable moment of tremendous bliss&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You keep me aware like a man on a cliff, solace me like a cocaine sniff&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re an antidote that cures me from numbness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, babe your elegance and grandeur kills my saneness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A glimpse of you is precious than a diamond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re eyes have such a depth, more intense than a laser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are like a portal to another dimension full of bliss and euphoria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a gracious blend of vivacity and elegance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/23/moonlight-revelation.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/23/moonlight-revelation.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Smile</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m willing to die for your lovely smile!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re like the moonlight in the veil of the night&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a lonely bird to travel a mile,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sing some songs in the tranquil night&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, babe but that lovely smile..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I’m willing to die for your lovely smile!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a lighthouse that guides the ship in the majestic night&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lost in the recesses of the colossal ocean, oh that tragic ship&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You solace that pitiful sailor, for your illumination&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have experienced bliss after a long while&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your smile glitters my face with joy and delight&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m willing to die for your lovely smile!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Smiling face like a chubby cat,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charming though like I fall flat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dominate my thoughts like a plutocrat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel so happy when we chit-chat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cannot be anymore a diplomat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you more than the stars above&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m willing to die for your lovely smile!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/22/smile.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/22/smile.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title> A Master &amp; A Disciple</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&quot;Don't insist upon your own fixed ideas.&lt;br /&gt;
 If your mind is broad it can easily embrace the entire world.&quot;&quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;- Zen Proverb&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A master is who broadens the vision and strengthens the endurance of a disciple. A master inculcates the discipline essential for the intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a subtle difference between a teacher and a guru. Teacher is just a profession and guru is a way of living. Teacher is of the west and a guru is of the east.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relationship between guru and disciple is intimate like love&lt;/strong&gt;. The reverence that is felt is like love but one difference: love is parallel and reverence is one above the other. Love creates friendship, because the lover and the loved one are on the same level. Reverence is also a kind of love but with a great difference: it is not on he same level, one person is higher. If there’s loving intimacy with the personality above, the reverence is not expected or demanded, but it is automatically created around the guru.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A guru is not aware of his guru-ship. A guru cannot claim that he is a guru. A guru has attended the condition of egolessness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The relationship between the disciple and the guru is a relationship of intimate trust.&lt;/strong&gt; That doesn’t mean blind faith, because the guru never expects you to believe in him — that is not an expectation.  Guru is always saying, “Jump into it! Do it!” But before you can jump, trust is needed or you will not jump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reverence for a teacher is not possible. It is forced, artificial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a guru, it happens automatically in the mind of the disciple. It’s the charisma of the guru which attracts the disciple like gravity. A teacher is knowledgeable but a master is intuitive and meditative. A teacher is ingrained with machine-like monotony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Even concepts such as beauty are not totally expressible&lt;/strong&gt; 
If you have seen a flower, you can say it is beautiful. But that does not convey anything. Your words never convey the actual realization of the moment because they can mean anything to the person to whom they are conveyed. A person who has never seen beauty in any flower will hear your words and understand the meaning of them without understanding anything at all, because the word beauty does not mean anything to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some indispensable revelations implied in the following poem:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: Baskerville font-size: 24px&quot;&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;You're a master and I'm your disciple,&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Not an instructor not an authority to order&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;But a master who observes, envelopes and loves his disciple&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;The wrath of your grandeur is calamitous&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Conventional wisdom is superficial&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;But your eccentric approach is altruistic&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;The way you teach is fabulous&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;The time spent in your lectures is eternal,&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Time ceased with each of your insightful revelation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Your talks are esoteric elevating me to the epitome of bliss&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Its my honor to be a disciple of a guru like you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;You make me feel bliss and get totally engrossed in learning too.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;p align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;-Rohit Naidu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/21/master-monk.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/21/master-monk.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>An essay on diligence and endurance</title>
            <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;every-strike-brings-me-closer-to-the-next-home-run&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;“Every strike brings me closer to the next home run.”&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;― Babe Ruth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Babe Ruth exhibits his triumphant philosophy through this prodigious statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/babe_ruth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;babe_ruth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;every-legend-was-once-a-beginner&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Every legend was once a beginner.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes them different is their perseverance and dedication. Most of you don’t want success as much as you want sleep. Pain will last for a minute or day. But if we quit it will last forever. Most of you don’t want success as much as you want sleep. We give up easily and we don’t climb our way towards the epitome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;I have heard an interesting anecdote:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A manager at a Company took a group of his employees to a golf course, where he introduced them to a virtuoso Golfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He made them watch him perform. He had a bunch of golf clubs , bats, pool sticks, anything you can think of that would be long and could be used to hit a golf ball. Out in the course were markers at 25, 50, 75, 100 yards on out to about 300 yards. This man went through a half hour display of hitting golf balls to these markers and landing every ball within about 2-feet of the marker. Hundreds of balls without fail. He was an absolute magician and could drive 300 yards, perfectly straight with a putter and hit a golf ball 100 yards (or to any marker) with a baseball bat just as well. It was unbelievable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this impressive display, the sales manager told the employees that he paid him                  $ 20,000 in cash to do that 30 minute show and paid for all of his expenses as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The showman told the employees the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I bet you’re wondering how I am so good at hitting golf balls and how I can command such a high price for this short display of my talents. It’s not that I am a gifted golfer. I don’t have a great score on the course when I play an actual game. It’s not that I have natural talent. It took me a very long time to get good at these things. It’s just that I wake up every day and do the following:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I hit golf balls for 2 hours, take a break, hit golf balls for 2 hours, take a lunch, hit golf balls for 2 hours, take a break, and hit golf balls for 2 more hours and finish for the day.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His simple point was that he gave 100% of his time to his job for those short bursts of time and didn’t waste his time at all while he was working at his job. That’s the secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a time where it is so easy to think that you are sneaking by with minimal work and still getting paid while you waste time on social media such as Facebook, Twitter and drag yourself into mediocrity…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, someone who is applying himself, 100% of the time is supposed to get ahead in life. You can be that person, if you live your live courageously and engrossing yourself into your work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;rohit-naidu&quot;&gt;Rohit Naidu&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;ty-dcp&quot;&gt;TY, DCP&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;154041&quot;&gt;154041&lt;/h6&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/20/diligence.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/02/20/diligence.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
